You win!
Tomorrow's battle will
be the final showdown.
We'll be launching a surprise
attack from the rear.
Once the Fortified City's forces
slow down the Combined Stratum Lords,
they'll send the signal for us to begin.
Does that about sum it all up, Hayachi?
Yep. Don't you worry.
The Guardian will certainly be able
to keep the Stratum Lords busy.
As for how, you'll just
have to wait and see.
They sure have a lot of faith
in this guardian of theirs.
I guess we should believe in him, too.
And once the Netherlord shows
his ugly mug, that'll be our cue.
That's when we strike.
It'll be up to us to get rid of
the Netherlord once and for all.
Does anyone have anything
they'd like to say?
I do.
I've got something I've been
wanting to get off my chest.
We surrendered ourselves to
the Netherlord once before.
For that, we should have died.
I wanted to thank you from the bottom
of my heart for taking us back.
Even if this battle's the end of the
line for us, I've got no regrets.
I feel the same way, my dear.
Our son's curse has been lifted.
There's nothing more I could ask for.
Yeah.
I get that you guys are pumped about this.
We definitely don't have
any plans to die here.
Right, Akka?
You can say that again.
There's no way I'm dying before I get a
girlfriend and we make out sloppy style.
You getting worked up for something so
pathetic makes me ashamed to be your brother.
Don't pay those fools any mind,
Kai. You have me. Damn it!
Let's do this!
Come on, everyone!
We'll burn bright until we burn out!
Not so fast now.
It doesn't burning out mean you die.
The captain's right, but we
should try to come back alive.
Don't just assume we won't.
Anyway, I suppose we should just do
what we always do then. Good idea.
We need to be around to watch our
granddaughter grow up, after all.
I would follow Master Boxo anywhere,
even if it meant marching
straight into Hell itself.
We vow to stand steadfast
by the Guardian's side.
Isn't that right, Usata? Usarion?
If anyone gets hurt, let me know.
I'll patch you up.
With the Director on our side, as
long as you're still breathing,
you'll be back in the fight in no time.
We'll be firing a ton of arrows,
so I don't want anyone getting hit.
And Pity will do her best. Promise.
As for me, I'll be driving an A-car around
with Shui and the director on board.
If you get hurt, I'll pick you up.
All right!
Wait, is it just me or is
something coming this way?
Hold on a sec, that's Botong.
And he's got people in tow!
My goodness, I thought that was it for me.
Thank you, you were a huge help.
Forgive me, God.
It's been far too long
since I prayed to you.
It's Director Baron Heavy.
I thought both of you were
at the Fortified City.
What happened?
It's the final showdown.
Instead of hiding away in the city,
we wanted to fight beside you all.
Also, you would have run
into trouble without me.
Not really.
We were fine. Right, Akka?
Yep, that's right, Shiro.
I'd even forgotten that you weren't here.
I've got the director by
my side, so I'm good to go.
You should have stayed.
Why'd you come?
Ah!
Team Poxo is finally all back together!
Um, I was gonna say something,
but I totally forgot!
Anyway, let's do our best, everyone!
Everybody's full of determination!
And they're plenty enthused!
All that's left is for the
final showdown to begin!
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul!
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner, Lamas!
The name's Boxxo. Hello there!
That means yes, by the way!
What are you, I mean to get it!
Going in to almost as a mission.
I need to stop by listening.
But you want to learn both of us,
Be able to do some of our tasks!
You know you don't know what it is?
Where the laughs, driving!
I am so much!
I have your sights.
Okay, I understand.
I'm so strict!
I am so strict!
You're the ultimate!
I'm in love.
Oh?
The destined day has arrived.
Our job today is to thin out
that tidal wave of monsters and
then defeat the huge frankenfreak
of stratum lord thingies.
This spot looks good.
What's up to all the
life forms in the soil?
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Field.
Sorry to harsh your buzz
and jam myself in here.
I'd like to have a little
chat with you if that's okay.
I don't mean to interrupt, but
is this really necessary, Field?
I don't actually have any
proof that it does anything.
But it feels easier to
manipulate the soil when I do it.
I had no idea.
I learned something new today.
Truth is, it's a mystery to me too.
I just kind of feel my
way through this stuff.
Awesome!
I have the land's permission.
So now I can go as crazy as I want.
Let's see here.
Where's the big fused up batty?
Of course, it's standing way in the back.
I couldn't ask for a more
perfect setup in my plan.
Time to get things started.
First I'll surprise them
with a little pit stop!
Have a nice trip, see you next fall!
I'll take my time consuming
those monsters later!
Too bad, they're nutrients now!
It's finally decided to bust a move!
Check out the size of that thing though!
How do I want to do this?
The vending machine
gang's probably watching
so I might as well put on a show for them!
So this is how I'll stop it!
Hiya!
Wap-a-chow!
Take that!
I'm not gonna let up!
Tell me, monster, can you smell
what this field is cooking?
What the heck?
My circuits can't handle
what's happening here!
Right now, the ground has arms
and legs, and it's fist fighting!
This makes no sense.
Matt's kind of creepy.
I thought so too, but I
didn't come out and say it.
Oh, wow, look at the Guardian go.
He's as dashing and gallant as ever.
Yeah, I had a feeling that was
Field taking care of business.
Now I feel kind of
silly for ever stressing
out over being reborn
as a vending machine.
Wait, is he making all
those pits appear too?
Yup, that's one of the Guardian's powers.
For real?
That's another thing Field can do?
This is no time for gawking.
We still have a job to do here!
You could even win a reward!
Fields taken on the Combined
Stratum Lord, Mano Alando.
Plus, he swallowed up a
bunch of the little guys.
First things first, we
need to open up a path.
Dance, O' Fire!
Shriek, O' Wind!
Oh, yeah!
This looks like my stuff!
Go on ahead!
He's charging it all by himself?
I know the director is strong, but
isn't that a little too reckless?
We're staying behind, too.
If someone doesn't stop
this horde of monsters here,
they'll get in your way when
you take on the Netherlord.
We're counting on you, Boxo!
Come back!
You got this! Kick his butt!
We'll be fine.
We'll see them again,
won't we? Hello there.
I'm not the only one who's anxious.
Guys, you better come back alive!
We need to stay focused
on the task at hand.
Even without his army, the
Netherlord won't be easy to defeat.
He's right.
They drew a ton of enemies away,
but there are still a ton left.
I must apologize.
We'll be stopping here to
give the Guardian a hand.
I wish you the best of luck!
And just like that, she's off.
It seems my sister is as restless as ever.
I'm sure her group will manage just fine.
Here's hoping everything goes as planned.
Hey, it's the Netherlord.
He's looking this way.
We did cause a big hubbub.
It makes sense he'd take notice of us.
How infuriating.
Thanks to your tiresome meddling,
my plans have been foiled again.
You will pay for your insolence.
It's pretty obvious from his
voice that he's pissed off at us.
He seems so angry, I couldn't resist
launching that to add some flair.
Flowers of light blooming on
the battlefield is a nice touch.
Very interesting.
Even now, you continue to mock me?
I actually thought it might calm you down.
Whoopsie!
My loyal servants, heed my call
and return from the path to Hades.
Master the power of the Netherlord and
punish these fools to defy your master!
Wait, those are the
Pinky and Thumb Generals!
And that's the Forefinger General,
but I defeated him back in the forest!
It looks like the Netherlord sacrificed a
bunch of monsters so he
could bring them back.
Three general class baddies.
If the Netherlord jumps in
two, we won't stand a chance.
I suppose it's time for
us to make our move.
It sure looks that way.
When's the last time we fought together?
It must have been forever in a day.
How do you know?
The Black Band is back together.
I never would have thought we'd get
a chance to team up like this again.
Seems long life has its advantages.
We'll take care of the three generals.
The Netherlord is all yours. Hold on!
Those guys are way too strong for
you to challenge them by yourselves.
We'll help you.
Yeah, she's right.
We should all be fighting together.
Sorry, but I can't allow that.
If the Netherlord were to unleash his magic
while we're in the middle of our battle,
we'd all be wiped out.
Because of that, someone needs to fight
him directly, or else we're sure to lose.
Everyone knows that it's up to seniors
like us to put on the boring opening act.
It's only right for us to let the
next generation take the spotlight.
If only I were 40 years younger,
I would have insisted on battling
it out with the Netherlord myself.
Ah, that really brings back memories.
The two of you were always so
hot-blooded back in the day.
Man, getting old sucks, huh?
One second, you're the main attraction,
but in the blink of an
eye, you're just sidekicks.
There you go.
There's no need to worry about us.
Also, I don't need to hear any
more complaining about getting old.
We were trying to be considerate,
but it seems we were just being
rude by worrying too much.
Don't have to tell me twice.
We're leaving the rest to you, Voxo.
Make sure you keep everyone safe.
Hello there.
Voxo!
When he summoned his generals, the
Netherlord probably used up a bunch of mana.
You can take him.
Activate Barrier!
The game plan is for
me to focus on defense.
and buy time while we wait
for the reinforcements?
from the fortified city.
Judging by how strong Field
is, the plan should work.
I'm guessing the Netherlord
understands that too.
I don't have time to
waste on you, sorry lot.
I'm going to settle this farce quickly.
Looks like someone's impatient.
For some reason, he's skipping his
usual routine of belittling us first.
What the heck?
He's created some kind of mini black hole.
There, you're wide open.
That won't save you.
My darkness sphere sucks everything
up into the spirit world.
It's impossible for you to resist it.
Sounds like he found a spell that
lets him get past my barrier.
Hold on, that's really bad.
What should we do now? I don't know.
Seriously, what do we do?
Crap, we're in big trouble.
Hey, Boxo!
You have to get bigger that
way you won't get sucked up.
Oh, that's right
Try picking me up now nether nerd you
must think you've outsmarted me with that?
This isn't looking good.
Now this is a problem.
This is looking bad.
Isn't there anything we can do? No!
Master Foxo! Not good. It's not good!
We're getting abducted!
I hope you enjoy your
journey to the spirit world!
How are the others doing?
Nice.
They're totally crushing it.
I might as well wrap things up here, too.
Chase Bielder!
All right, time to cook on the
final dish with maximum destruction.
I've decided to make some rock skewers.
Our main ingredient is a big
fresh rock in the shape of a dog.
And the skewer is gonna be yours truly.
I'll make a point out of
selectively bred burdock roots.
Thanks to generations of careful
breeding, I've created this masterpiece?
that's even harder than tempered steel.
What's more?
If I use vines to add a truckload of
torque to the already ultra-heavy tip,
it'll at least double the skewering power.
Or I think that's what
I read in a manga once.
This is the spirit world?
It looks like the
aftermath of an apocalypse.
There's not a single living thing here.
This place feels so lonely.
How am I supposed to find
tasty food to eat in here?
This is scary.
I don't like it.
In a world devoid of people,
there can be no footwear.
What a nightmare.
I was expecting there to be more of the
Netherlord's minions running around.
Guess I was wrong.
What do we do?
Psst. Uh-oh. Time.
We can't wait around
for something to happen.
We have to hurry and get back.
No need to worry about that, because
you'll all be dead soon enough.
The Netherlord.
Cooking complete.
Too bad for you,
but one of the main
reasons you lost is that
you didn't have enough fiber in your diet.
Well done, Field!
Yeah, you really knocked him dead.
You're as amazing as ever, Sir Guardian.
I guess Hayachi snuck in at
some point during the battle.
Everyone did well.
Let's have a victory party
once this is all over.
Wait a sec.
I don't see Boxxo in the others anywhere.
Boxxo, huh?
That's the name of that
vending machine guy.
I thought they were supposed
to be fighting the Netherlord.
Where the heck did they go?
Did they get magic to weigh somewhere?
Huh? Huh?
Look there, Guardian!
Something's happening!
It's back!
As long as the Netherlord is alive,
it looks like it'll keep reviving.
He's the one controlling it, so it
makes sense he's got to go down first.
Jace, this is a real pain in the butt.
We'll have to take care
of this thing first.
We'll leave the Netherlord to you guys.
As a fellow otherworldly traveler,
I have faith in you, Boxxo.
You trapped us in here.
Why'd you bother coming in?
Yes, yes.
I'll take this opportunity
to finish you off.
That magic item in
particular must be destroyed.
I won't allow something that
exceeds my expectations to exist.
I see.
So he followed us in here to make sure
I was destroyed for good this time.
Isn't that special?
So if we beat you here,
it'll help out everybody else
who's fighting on the other side.
She's right.
Let's kick the skeleton's
big bony butt. Yeah.
He's done for.
We'll bury him here.
You must be punished for sending me to a
world without a single piece of footwear.
With this, I'll sever
our cursed connection.
If I so desired, I could simply
crush you like insects right now.
That portal links back to your world.
And upon my death, it will become active.
That should serve as motivation.
Nice of him to do that, but who
knows if it's just another trick.
You guys try to keep the Netherlord busy.
While you're fighting, I'll investigate
to see if that portal's legit.
I wouldn't waste my time lying to you.
While I resent the fact that you've
thwarted my plans again and again,
in my view, it makes you worthy foes.
Because of that, you will have the
distinct honor of dying by my hand.
That's a good point.
He may be an evil skeleton hellbent
on conquering the whole world,
but he's never lied to us.
If we were to fight here,
your concern for that woman would
keep you from fully using your powers.
Changing things up, huh?
You're not hiding behind
hostages or traps anymore?
I've decided the best way to defeat you is
to utterly crush you
with overwhelming power.
That way you won't be able to say you
only lost because of dirty tricks.
Now, attack me however you'd like.
Because I'm feeling generous,
I promise not to fight back.
I'll let you experience true despair.
Fine!
Ready or not, here I come!
You wield considerable power,
But unfortunately for you,
it's not enough to shatter
the barrier of darkness.
Considerable power, huh?
He can tell how strong it was even
though it didn't leave a scratch.
Let's see if you can handle
this one through Rolling Strike!
I wonder if he can see his mana depleting.
Kind of like when my points go down
whenever my barrier takes a hit.
Standing here and simply taking
your attacks is getting dull.
Perhaps I should have a little bit of fun.
Come on, now.
Did you forget what you said
about not fighting back?
Unless our attacks are actually working?
Fighting back!
Oh, don't flatter yourself.
I've just grown tired of waiting. Too bad!
I can tell he's glaring at me with
those beady little light balls.
Maybe I should cool it with
the taunting for a bit!
Guess it's his turn to attack now.
We'll pull through this!
And figure out a way to
turn the tables on him?
I don't know.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
I look forward to serving you again.